<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Moor | Open Source Ninja</title>
    <link>http://tim.moor.kiwi/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tim Moor | Open Source Ninja</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tim.moor.kiwi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ARC INNOVATIONS</title>
      <link>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/arc-innovations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/arc-innovations/</guid>
      <description>Originally taken on a 6 month contract to conduct a review and replacement of Arc&amp;rsquo;s aging EMC SAN Technology this role quickly expanded to include the implementation of vmwares first release of vCloud Director and the creation of a Service Orientated Architecture platform.
I took on this role at Arc Innovations to allow myself to gain a deeper understanding of technology and be involved for the first time in ground up solution deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHRISTCHURCH CITY COUNCIL</title>
      <link>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/christchurch-city-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/christchurch-city-council/</guid>
      <description>Excited and eager to learn more about the IT Industry, the move to Christchurch and the assignment as the Business Systems Administrator of the Government Enterprise Management Suite (GEMS) applications was a true honour.
With 450 daily active users and being a member of a small team meant that in the beginning with my days were managing database, windows and application administration tasks.
Over time a picked up PERL and used this as the tool to automate a large majority of these manual tasks, such as creating a web socket load balancer to spread users across varying application servers or auto mating database loads from SAP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIMENSION DATA</title>
      <link>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/dimension-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/dimension-data/</guid>
      <description>This was my first role in what I considered the big time, after 6 years for working for small to medium size New Zealand based companies, this was my first experience working for a large multinational corporation. No longer supporting a single customer, this role saw me managing 300+ systems across many difference customers, which brought with it a number of challenges. Often being pulled in different direction, this role taught me that : Time management, team work, planning and agility were key factors to success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOODSTUFFS</title>
      <link>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/foodstuffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/foodstuffs/</guid>
      <description>Foodstuffs was my first appointment managing people, while I had taken on roles of leadership within teams like WML and project roles as in the council before, this was the first time that I had direct reports and the process that came with it. This was a new role within Foodstuffs and I was given the remit to implementing and control process across the organsiation. This included tasks such as implementing an Event Management application to asses change and outages quickly, through to tracking Key Performance Indicators for the company core systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RED HAT INC</title>
      <link>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/red-hat-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/red-hat-inc/</guid>
      <description>The life of a consultant is not one for the faint hearted. Early morning starts and 14 hour days are common place. A role where you think on your feet and where “Always be prepared” was no longer the moto just for the scouts.
Due to my attention to detail and service delivery focus, I am often brought into pre-sales engagements to run compressed architecture and design workshops to discover and document requirements and assist with transitioning high level business requirements into effective designs and chargeable statements of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WEBBIZ MEDIA LIMITED</title>
      <link>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/webbiz-media-limited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tim.moor.kiwi/jobs/webbiz-media-limited/</guid>
      <description>Formed in 2001, WML Software provides professional services focused on custom software and web solutions for Mitre 10 New Zealand. As the service desk managed I was the voice of the organsiation to the staff from their 125 stores nation wide.
Providing first level support to start with, over time I grew to see the patterns and common pain points of our clients. With little or no experience of the Linux platform I sat down and studied hard to understand a way that I could prevent the customers from having to call.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>